Nanab Banana Pro is the first AI model
able to generate complete e-commerce
listings completely indistinguishable
from professional photography and
design. But it only works if you know
how to prompt it. I've launched over
3,000 e-commerce products online and I'm
one of the single top spenders of Amazon
ads on the platform. And these are the
prompts my team is using to create
profitable Amazon listings using [music]
Google's AI image generator, Nano Banana
Pro. And I won't be just covering the
prompts, but also how to use reference
images and how to use the chat to come
out with the best possible output that's
completely indistinguishable from a
professionally designed image. We're
going to go through examples in pets,
home and kitchen, supplements, beauty,
and other categories. And I'm going to
cover one huge mistake that brand owners
always make that completely stops them
from being able to use this tool
properly for their listings. [music]
Even some of the smartest brand owners I
know are still making this mistake.
Later on in the video, I'm also going to
give you access to a full guide to using
NanoBanana Pro for e-commerce listings
that includes a prompting chart that you
can download for free for yourself. Now,
there are two strategies for prompting.
One is typing in your prompt in natural
language. And this strategy is the
simplest, but even this one, you have to
know how to do it right and what types
of words to use. I'm going to cover that
all in this video. But the second
strategy is instead of writing the
prompts yourself, you get AI to write
your prompts for you. So instead of
writing out the prompt in natural
language, you get chatbt or claude or
Gemini itself to write your prompt and
then you can make small edits and use
that prompt to generate the image that
you want. We'll cover both of these
prompting strategies in this video cuz
both are totally different approaches,
but both can work great. You can use the
prompts you're going to learn in this
video to generate your primary image for
your e-commerce listing. The lifestyle
and inuse shots, the benefits graphic,
the features graphic, competitor
comparison graphics, instructional
step-by-steps, dimensions, and in fact,
I'm going to give you a list of 22
potential ideas for images that you can
generate with AI or without AI, all in
this ebook that I'm going to be linking.
It's a free ebook in the description of
this video. It goes through each of the
different images that you can put on
your listing that generate high
conversion rates and you can pick based
on your particular product category
which ones to put in your image set for
your e-commerce listing. Now, before we
get into how to generate each of these
particular images, let's just talk about
the two different types of prompting.
Natural language prompting and prompting
using AI to write your prompts. So,
check out this very simple prompt that I
used to get this output for this beauty
product. All I did was give the model
some reference images and give it the
output that I want and a few vibe words.
So, I told the model that I was going to
use this image as the primary image on
an Amazon listing. That's really
important because just telling it what I
was going to use it for gives the model
everything it needs to know about how to
optimize it for that particular use.
It's going to be optimizing color,
contrast, size, ratio, scale, all
because it knows the output. So, this is
the first big mistake that a lot of
sellers make when they're prompting with
Gemini and Nano Banana Pro is they try
to be too specific. They really just
don't give the model enough credit. You
don't have to say use this camera model
and put it on a white background and
then the actual like, you know, code for
the white like # RGB5555.
You don't have to do that because this
isn't a dumb machine. This isn't like a
command prompt from your first Mac
computer when you were a kid. Well, I'm
just talking to people my generation, I
guess, where you had command prompts and
you actually had to type in like start
Windows. It's not a dumb algorithm. You
have to talk to it actually like a
person, like a skilled person. So, it's
okay to just say what you want as the
output and then trust that it will know
what's important based on that. So, you
don't have to list all of the things.
You don't have to say, you know, white
background with a very slight shadow,
um, high contrast label, a shine on the
bottle, and listing all these things
because the model actually knows what's
important based on the output you're
going to use it for. So, if you tell it
the output that you're going to use it
for and any critical information that it
might not know, even based on that
output, that's really all you need to
say. So, vibe words actually work really
well. like the the feel or the vibe
actually is more important for you to
communicate than specific details of the
image. You could see me doing this in
this prompt where I was generating a
lifestyle image for this product. So, I
said, "Create a lifestyle image to be
used in the Amazon listing of a
millennial mom using this diffuser in
her cozy home office." I said cozy
because I know that's the vibe that
people using an essential oil diffuser
are going for. They're trying to relax.
They're trying to be cozy. They're
trying to be higgy. And this word tells
the model everything it needs to know
about everything else. So I don't have
to say make sure that there's baskets in
the photo and a plant in there. I just
gave it the vibe that I want the photo
to have and it understands that. So if
you have the final output and the use
and you have the vibes in there, you're
already going a really long way towards
natural language prompting. Now, another
thing specifically for e-commerce that
you have to take into consideration when
you're using natural language to prompt
an image like this is you have to make
sure that it knows that it should be
optimized for mobile. This isn't as
important for lifestyle images like this
one that I was mentioning here, but it
gets really important when you're
generating graphics. Here's an example
of a mobile optimized competitor
comparison graphic that we generated
using just some raw phone photos of the
supplement product. Now, if we didn't
say in the prompt mobile optimized, it
wouldn't have come out this way with
text big enough to see on a phone
screen. Here's another one that we
generated making sure to include mobile
optimized because it had to be simple
enough to be read on a phone and big
enough to be read on a phone. So,
remember when natural language
prompting, you don't have to go super
detailed on everything. Just give it the
vibe and give it the most important use
case or output that you're going to use
the image for. I.e., just [music] tell
it that this is going to be on an
e-commerce listing or an Amazon listing.
Make sure to say mobile optimized. And
some vibe words that tend to work well
for me include uh clean, modern,
aesthetic. When I use words like that, I
end up getting cleaner shots. To create
this features graphic, for example, all
I did was upload some reference images
from my phone and I used the prompt,
create a clean aesthetic features
graphic to be used on an Amazon listing.
Make sure the final image is mobile
optimized. And it came out with this,
which was actually really good. And
you'll notice I didn't even give it the
features to use in the image. I could
have said make a clean aesthetic
features graphic to be used on an Amazon
listing with the following features and
then list feature one, feature two,
feature three, feature four, and then
said make sure the final image is mobile
optimized. So, this is where it depends
on how lazy you want to be. There's
doing this on easy mode where you
literally are letting the AI do the
thinking for you. Or if you have some
things that you know you want to show,
especially when you're talking about
graphics that have text like a features
graphic, a benefits graphic, competitor
comparison, an instructional graphic,
then and you know like what the
instructions should be or what the
competitor comparison points should be
or what the feature should be, then you
should list them out. But sometimes it
is fun just to see what the AI would do.
And a lot of times, like in this case,
it actually came out with really good
content, even though I didn't even tell
it what to do. In this example, for the
same product, I did actually list out
the steps that I wanted it to include,
but I didn't have to. I could have let
the AI figure that out itself. Now,
let's talk about reference images. So,
providing really good reference images
is actually more important than the
prompt. So, the images that you put in
as the input are part of the prompt
[music] and interact directly with the
prompt. So, right from the get- go,
let's look at this example where I was
creating the Amazon listing for this
diffuser. I made sure that one of the
reference images was a close-up of the
buttons because they have very tiny
engravings and I wanted to make sure the
AI got that right. If I hadn't done
that, it wouldn't have gotten the
engravings right. But you can see if you
zoom way in on this image, it got the
engravings, the little engravings on the
buttons just right because I gave it the
proper reference images to be able
[music] to know that detail. So getting
different zoom distances and different
angles and also showing the product in a
hand or in another setting that gives a
sense of scale and size is the most
important part when getting e-commerce
listing images right. But there is
another secret and an even cooler way to
use reference images when you're
prompting. And I'll tell you that after
I take a sip of my grapefruit juice.
It's going to piss some people off. Man,
did you guys get pissed off in my last
nanobanana tutorial when I was eating
berries?
All the comments were just don't eat.
Don't eat while you're talking. This is
gross. This video is disgusting. I had
no idea how many people out there have
misophonia. But anyways, so yeah, and
I'm on grapefruit juice cuz I don't do
caffeine now. Um, so I'm no longer
drinking my Hojicha tea sadly. But it's
okay cuz grapefruit juice has lots of
vitamin C and that keeps me from getting
sick in the winter. So let's get back to
the subject at hand. Using reference
images that aren't your product, but are
the vibe that you want the final output
to be is a total hack when generating
e-commerce listing images. So, we wanted
to create a really viby, natural type of
looking image for this beauty product.
So, what we did was we found an image
that already looked like the final
output that we wanted online and we told
the model to use that as a reference.
So, it said, "Using the provided
lifestyle reference image as
inspiration, create a similar premium
minimalistic skincare lifestyle scene."
And then we gave some additional context
to the model and it outputed this, which
we thought looked good. By the way,
credit to Elena on our team. She's the
one that used this prompt. This is also
how we created this striking vibrant
Florida shot that we generated using
Nanabanana Pro for a supplements
product. Shout out to David on our team
who generated this one. Now, here's
another trick for those of you that are
light on credits cuz you're running out
of image credits with all the Dana
Banana Pro images that you're prompting
is you prompt it to generate four images
at once. So, for this water pouring can,
I said create four lifestyle images for
this watering can, showing the four top
use cases for the can, make them
aesthetic and cozy. They will be used on
an Amazon listing. And I got these four
images. Then I can choose which one I
like best. And I can say make a full res
version of the upper left image, the one
that I like the most. So, this helps you
save image credits, first of all, and
second of all, give you gives you more
at bats, meaning you get more ideas um
and more chances for one of them to be
really good, and then you just tell it
to upscale the one that you like. Okay,
so what we're going to do is we're going
to ask AI to help us write a prompt to
then put into the AI to generate the
image that we want. And why would we do
this? We do this if we want to have
really tight control over what image is
generated and be able to edit specific
things. So a very easy way to do this is
literally just say to Gemini, "Help me
write a prompt to be used in Nano Banana
Pro AI image generator for a watering
can product or whatever your product is
for a lifestyle image I can use on my
Amazon listing for the product. I will
provide reference images of the product
along with the prompt." And so then
Gemini is going to spit out some options
of prompts for you. So, it gave me an
option for cozy indoor house plant
focus, a vibrant outdoor garden focus,
and a modern urban balcony minimalist
focus. So, I'm going to do a little
split test here where I'm going to copy
this prompt in from Gemini so you could
see what kind of output we get there
verbatim. And then I'm going to put in a
natural language prompt and you'll see
what kind of output we get there. And
we'll show this the two side by side so
you can see the difference. So, first
I'm going to copy this prompt that it
gives me. And you'll notice it has a few
different characteristics. So it says
subject, environment, lighting, style,
constraints, and the environment says a
bright modern living room. The lighting
is soft diffused window light, morning
sun. So this is the benefit of having AI
help you write the prompts. Is that you
can then go in and say, "Oh, I didn't
even think about it, but really no, I
don't want outdoor light. I want it to
be indoor light because most people that
use my product are in an office." And
then you can go in and just edit just
that part of the prompt. then it gives
you more control over the output,
especially if you have a very specific
vision for it. But we're not going to do
that now. All we're going to do is copy
and paste this prompt in. Just going to
remove it. Has a little input here.
We'll remove that. We'll add our
reference images here. We have three of
them. And then we'll see what our output
is when we use AI to write our prompt
for us. Okay. So, here's the result we
got. Really not bad. Pretty good
lifestyle image for this product. Shows
it in use. It is accurate in terms of
the dimensions of the product. This is
something that we could or would use on
the e-commerce listing or the Amazon
listing for this product. So, pretty
good. Now, let's see what we get if we
just use a natural language prompt.
Okay, so here I uploaded the exact same
three reference images and all I said
was create a lifestyle image for this
product in use to be used on an Amazon
listing for the product. And here's what
I got, which I think is somewhat
equivalent to the last image. This one
is a little bit more realistic. It looks
kind of like somebody's house, but it is
still a very high quality shot. So, if
you compare these two images side by
side, I would say they're pretty much a
tie. They either one could be used on an
Amazon listing, they're both pretty high
quality. The difference is in this image
where we used AI to generate our prompt
instead of just natural language, we
could have edited any of those specific
details before we generated the image.
by editing that prompt about the
lighting, about the setting, about the
environment, about the photography
style, um the brand identity, all of
that stuff we could have changed prior
to inputting the prompt and edited it so
that we had a little bit more control
over the final output. Now, if you want
a full walkthrough of generating a
complete Amazon listing just using Nano
Banana Pro, I put a link to a guide.
It's the ultimate guide to NanoBanana
Pro for Amazon sellers. It's in the
description of this video. It's the
first link in the description of the
video. You can click there to download
that for free right now. So, if you want
to walk through on your own time after
you watch this video, I recommend you
clicking that link below this video in
the description. You can download that
for free. Okay. Now, what I'm going to
do is go through some very simple
natural language prompts that work to
generate specific images for e-commerce
and Amazon listings. And I'm going to go
through them rapid fire. Each example we
go through, you're going to see the
prompt itself and an example output that
comes from that specific [music] exact
prompt. So, here we have create a clean
photo rendering of this product to be
used as the primary image on an Amazon
listing. This is great to create the
primary image. A lot of times it works
on the first try. And if it doesn't work
on the first try, sometimes you just
have to chat back and forth once or
twice to get the final image. Like in
this case where it gave the product a
shine, a glossy shine where it actually
had a matte finish. So, I just had to
say try again, but with a matte finish
instead of a shiny finish. And then it
gave me a primary image that was ready
to upload. Okay. Now, for lifestyle
images, a prompt that works is create a
lifestyle image of a avatar. You put in
your avatar here using this product in
[music] setting. And that's where you
put the setting in. This image is to be
used in the Amazon listing for this
product. So, example, you might say,
create a lifestyle image of a millennial
mom using this product in her home
office. This image is to be used in the
Amazon listing image for this product.
and you would upload reference images
along with this prompt. When it comes to
lifestyle images, a great hack is to ask
it to do four at once because then you
can just select the one that you like
more and you have more shots at actually
getting something that you like. So you
just say create four lifestyle images
for avatar using this product in setting
to be used on an Amazon listing and then
it'll generate a four panel and you
choose the one you like and say upscale
that one. Here's a prompt for creating
features graphics. So, the prompt is
make a clean aesthetic features graphic
for this product to be used on an Amazon
listing. Make sure the final image is
mobile optimized. Now, if you know what
features you want to include, you can
include those features with a prompt
like this that actually lists out each
of the four features that you want to
include. Okay, now let's talk benefits
graphic where you're showing the main
benefits of the product. The prompt that
works is make a clean aesthetic benefits
graphic to be used on an Amazon listing
for this product with the following
benefits and then list out the benefits
and say make sure the final image is
mobile optimized. If you don't want to
list out the benefits, just like in the
features graphic, you can leave them out
and just see what the AI generates and
just edit it if you think one or two of
them should change. Now, competitor
comparison graphic. Here's a prompt that
works for that. Another image that can
have a really high impact on your actual
conversion rate of your e-commerce or
Amazon listing. Create a simple, modern,
and clean competitor comparison graphic
of this product to be used on an Amazon
listing. Make sure it is mobile
optimized. Again, if you actually have
the attributes that you want it to
include in the comparison, then you'd
say, create a simple, modern, and clean
competitor comparison graphic of this
product to be used on an Amazon listing,
highlight the following attributes, and
then list the attributes out 1 through
4. And then make sure it is mobile
optimized. So, those are the prompts for
some of the images that lead to a high
conversion rate on an Amazon listing or
an e-commerce listing. But those are
just a few examples. There's actually 22
different types of images that you could
generate either with AI or not with AI.
And I am leaving a link to a guide that
walks through examples of each of those
different 22 image options in the
description of this video. You can also
see them here on the screen. There are
some other ones that we haven't covered
today, like ingredients list, nutrition
facts, uh before and after shots, that's
great for beauty compatibility, that's
good for products that work with other
products. Material quality, what's
included, size guide and size
comparison, guarantee, warranty. These
are all different images that can work
really well to help you drive higher
conversion rate. Obviously, you don't
want to have all 22 of them, but you
choose the ones that are most well
suited for your particular product. So,
I recommend you guys download that guide
in the description of this video as
well. Now, my team does a ton of this
because our whole business is to partner
with brands and grow them profitably on
Amazon, primarily using Amazon PBC, but
also click-through rate and conversion
rate improvement strategies, which Nano
Banana Pro now helps out a lot with. If
you're looking for a partner to help you
grow profitably using Amazon PBC, you
might qualify to partner with us to help
you do that. You can find out if you
qualify in the link in the description
of this video. It's sophiew.com. So, if
that's interesting to you, I'll see you
over there. And if you want to see a
full master class on using NanoBanana
Pro for e-commerce business owners and
brand owners and Amazon sellers, check
out this video here where I walk through
all of the main principles and you
actually walk through the creation of
one full Amazon listing with me. So, I
recommend you check that out here and
I'll see you over there.
[music]